Jasper 别动 不要扭来扭去的
Jasper, hold still.,Stop squirming.Hold still.
他这次又干什么了?
What did he do now?
他又打了一架
He got in another fight.
鼻血止不住
And I can't get his nose to stop bleeding.
得用点劲
You have to apply much more,pressure than that.
你非今天惹事不可
You had to do this today.
我工作了一天 本该和院长一起吃饭的
I got office hours.,Supposed to have dinner with the dean.
你不能一生气就这么发作
You just can't lash out,whenever you get angry.
他说我闻起来像个猴子
He said I smell like a monkey.
确实是 你不能一边拒绝洗澡
Well, you do.You can't refuse to,take a bath
一边打那些说你臭的孩子 该死!
and then hit kids who tell you,that you smell.Damn!
你不觉得我们该打911?
Don't you think we should call 911?
这不是第一次出鼻血 他会好的
This isn't his first nosebleed.,He'll be fine.
- 爸爸!,- 嘿 小鹅Lucy
- Daddy!,- Hey, lucy-goosey.
- 我在扮演医生,- 我也是
- I'm playing doctor.,- So am I.
回去继续演吧
can you go back and play?
- 什么时候打的架?,- 十多分钟前
- When was this fight?,- Over ten minutes ago.
我觉得头晕
I feel dizzy.
- 打911吧,- 好的
- Maybe you should make that call.,- Okay.
爸爸 看 我能帮忙
Daddy, look.I can help.
不 别了 亲爱的
No--that's great, honey.
你能不能别烦爸爸?
Can you just please leave daddy alone?
这儿有个孩子鼻血止不住 请快点
one of my kids is bleeding profusely,from the nose.Please hurry.
派出救护车了
They're sending an ambulance.
让车别来了
Call them back.
他会没事的
He'll be fine.
你觉得怎么样 兄弟?
How you feeling, bud?
- 头晕吗?,- Lucy
- You light headed?,- Lucy.
上帝啊
Oh my god.
Lucy 你还好吗?
Lucy, are you okay?Lucy.
Lucy 你怎么样?
Lucy, are you okay?
-=怪杰医生豪斯=-,第三季 第19集,"人小鬼大"; "Act Your Age"
House,Season 03 Episode 19
看在上帝的份上
Oh, for god's sake.
停下 别动
Stop.Don't move.
柔和的夜光照亮你的双眼
The way the soft...evening light,catches your eyes.
薄暮爱抚你的发丝 当你转身时
The gentle caress of dusk on your hair,as you turn around
离开办公室 别给我那病历
and leave my office,without giving me that file.
- 限制性心包炎,- 无聊
- Restrictive pericarditis.,- Boring.
- 她上幼儿园,- 比无聊好一点
- She's in kindergarten.,- Less boring.
留级读幼儿园的老奶奶
Or grandma's been held back a few years.
钙化了 还有高血压
It's calcified and she's hypertensive.
给她做手术会比较好
Better get her into surgery.
她已经在做手术了
She already is in surgery.
手术复杂 需要一整晚
Tricky procedure.Gonna take all night.
睡踏实些
Sleep tight.
没有先天缺陷 没有健康问题
No congenital defects,no health problems.
但她的心脏在勒死自己
But her heart is strangling itself.
吸引人
Fascinating.
心包膜病理报告要等到在手术完才有
Since the pathology on the pericardium,won't be back until after they remove it.
从她的血液开始 可以测病毒,细菌感染...
Get started on her blood.you can test,for viral infections,bacteria...
围捕常见的疑犯
round up the usual suspects.
淀粉样变性病 肉状瘤病 血色沉着病...
Amyloidosis,sarcoidosis,hemochromatosis...
疯狂干吧 检查所有病
heck. Go wild.Do all the osises.
全都要查 睡踏实些
All taken care of.Sleep tight.
已经包围心脏了
this thing is already all around her heart.
要是进入心肌 她就死了
If it gets into the muscle,she's dead.
最有可能是柯萨奇病毒
Best bet is coxsackie virus.
细小病毒b-19 巨细胞病毒...
Parvovirus b-19,cmv...
紧迫包围更有可能是细菌性感染
bacterial infection's more likely,to turn constrictive.
- 可能是结核病毒,- 是啊
- It could be tb.,- Right.
忘了她曾在苏联古拉格集中营待过
Forgot about the part where she did time,in a russian gulag.
她的血细胞比容上升了
Her hematocrit's elevated.
多一点红细胞什么都不说明
A few extra red blood cells means nothing.
她可能只是脱水
She's probably just dehydrated.
我也可以举出三四种现象,符合我的理论
Yes, and I could assume three or four things,to fit my theory too.
她病了 显然没有喝--
She's sick.She obviously,hasn't been drinking--
够了!
enough!
我估计你们不睡在一起了吧?
I take it you two aren't,sleeping together anymore?
我们按House说的做所有检查
We do what house said.,We test for everything.
好的
Good.
我回家了
Then I can go home.
什么时候开始 我们不包括你了?
Since when does we not include you?
不管怎样 House都会叫我们傻瓜的
Well, house is gonna call us idiots anyway.
不如做个休息充足的傻瓜
Might as well be a well-rested idiot.
你们这些傻瓜
You guys are idiots.
为什么?
Why?
因为我们熬夜做你要求的事?
Because we stayed up all night,doing exactly what you told us to do?
不 因为你们熬夜照我要求的做
No, because you stayed up all night,doing exactly what I told you to do
却没有可看的结果
and have nothing to show for it.
我们排除了许多错误答案
We eliminated dozens of wrong answers.
我问你们2加2等于多少
I asked you what two plus two equals.
一天以后 你们告诉我不等于25
And a day later,you tell me, not 25.
病理报告刚出来
Pathology report just got filed.
在Lucy的心包膜上找到肉芽瘤
Found granulomas in lucy's pericardium.
意味着真菌感染
Indicates a fungal infection.
干的好
Nice work.
他回家了
He went home.
苦干不如巧干
Work smart, not hard.
找出是什么真菌 做淋巴结活检
Find out which fungus.,Biopsy a lymph node.
和"本月最佳雇员" 一起去
Take "employee of the month" with you.
- 我宁愿和foreman--,- 我知道
- I would rather foreman--,- I know.
- 我不想再打针了,- 我不想再打针了
- I don't want anymore shots.,- I don't want anymore shots.
看着我 抓紧我的手 好吗
Look at me, goosey.Squeeze my hand,okay?
这能告诉我们你为什么病了,才能治好你
This will tell us why you're sick,,so we can make you all better.
她会从哪感染真菌?
Where would she pick up a fungus?
任何潮湿的地方 水池旁边,储物间 公共浴室
Anywhere moist.Around a pool,,locker room,public shower.
她没有上体操或游泳课
She doesn't have any gym or swim classes.
她甚至不喜欢和孩子在外面玩
She doesn't even,like to play with kids outside.
有没有出去旅行过 去了什么地方?
Haven't taken any trips?,Gone anywhere new?
自从他们的妈妈...就不怎么出门了
It's been hard to get away...,since their mom.
我妈妈去世了
My mom's dead.
- 我很抱歉,- 去年
- I'm sorry.,- Last year.
脑瘤
Brain cancer.
你要把那个插到她的胳膊里 酷!
You're gonna stick that thing,in her arm?Cool!
酷的是 你妹妹不会有感觉
The cool part is,,your sister won't feel a thing.
项链很漂亮
Nice necklace.
谢谢
Thanks.
你喜欢电玩吗?
You like videogames?
喜欢
Love them.
可以了
That should do it.
你还好吗?
You okay?
要我的小兔子
I want my bunny.
你在淘气吗?
Are you being silly?
我不知道该拿哪一只
I don't know which one to take.
什么意思 发生什么了?
What do you mean?What's happening?
复视能告诉我们什么?
So what does the double vision tell us?
裂隙灯检查表明眼睛前腔肿大 葡萄膜炎
Slit lamp revealed the eye's anterior,chamber is swollen.Uveitis.
意味着不是术后反应,也不是神经学问题
Means it's not a post-op effect,and it's not neurological.
也不是真菌 淋巴结活检正常
It's not fungal either.,The lymph node biopsy was clean.
所以我们退回原点了
So we're back to square one.
有一点进展 排除了两种可能
One and a half.,We've eliminated two more conditions.
是 2加2也不等于12或16
Yes.Two plus two doesn't equal 12 or 16 either.
视觉问题和发病的心脏,等于某种自体免疫病
Vision issues plus screwy heart,equals some type of auto-immune.
狼疮和川崎病是六岁儿童中最常见的
Lupus and kawasaki's are the most common,in a six-year-old.
是 难得有不得狼疮,和川崎病的六岁孩子
Yeah, tough to find a six-year-old,who doesn't have lupusor kawasaki'S.
你有没有看过她的膝盖?
Did you look at her knees?
就是腿中间那块凸起
Those knobby things in the,middle of her legs.
有没有疤或者痂?
Any scars or scabs?
- 和这有什么关系...,- 大部分六岁孩子常会弄伤自己
- What does that have to do...,- most six-year-olds hurt themselves a lot.
骑自行车乱撞 爬树 蹦极跳
The crash their bikes,,climb trees, bungee jump.
爸爸说她不喜欢在户外乱跑
Dad said she doesn't like to run,around outside.
因为在外面跑会疼
Because running around outside hurts.
她从没提起...
She didn't mention anything about...
六岁孩子不熟悉 "我关节发炎了",这样的句子
most six-year-olds are not familiar,with the phrase,"my joints feel inflamed."
所以2加2等于...
So two plus two equals...
幼年型类风湿性关节炎
juvenile rheumatoidarthritis.
查抗核抗体来确认,类固醇治疗视觉问题
We're checking her ana to confirm and,giving her steroids to fix her vision.
有个傻瓜给了我两张今晚的戏票
Some idiot gave me two tickets,for a play tonight.
救过他的命,显然值186美元呢
Saved his life.,Apparently worth $186.
抱歉 我刚去撒尿了
Sorry,I had to take a leak.
我...我不知道你有病人
Oh, I...I didn't know,you were seeing a patient.
这是检查室 你以为我在干什么?
It's an exam room.,What did you think I was doing?
你常干的事--躲避Cuddy
What you usually do--hiding from cuddy.
躲这儿就太傻了,这儿有个病人
Be stupid to do it in here.,There's a patient in here.
- 最近有没贪杯?,- 嗯 没有 我...
- You been drinking more?,- Uh, no, I...
这家伙尿频
guy's peeing all the time.
这场戏 有兴趣么?
The play, interested?
当然了 要我去接你么?
Sure.You want me to pick you up?
- 我不去的,- 你说有两张票的
I'm not going.You said two tickets.
你以为是约会?
You thought this was a date?
- 其他症状?,- 肚子疼
- Any other symptoms?,- My stomach hurts.
背痛 肌肉酸痛 头晕眼花
I have back pain and muscle aches.,I feel dizzy.
上课不能集中注意力
And I have trouble concentrating,sometimes in class.
我真的该...
I really should...
票你要是不要?
you want the tickets or not?
- 为什么不和我一起?,- 这是看戏啊
- Why don't you wanna go with me?,- It's a play.
男人去看戏肯定是被女人拖去的
Dudes only go to plays,if they're dragged by women
只是想一窥春光
they're hoping to see naked.
那为什么给我票?
So why are you giving them to me?
也许你有人想要一窥的
Maybe there's someone you wanna see naked.
我--
I--
好吧
all right.
- 发热?,- 没有
- Any fever?,- No.
- 尿液中有杂质?,- 没有
- Anything in your pee other than pee?,- No.
- 需要尿样,- 不行
- I'm gonna need a urine sample.,- No.
上一句可不是问句
Yeah, that last one wasn't a question.
- 你可能有糖尿病,- 当着别人的面我尿不出来
- You might have diabetes.,- I can't pee in public.
有洗手间
We have bathrooms.
在公共洗手间尿不出来
I can't pee in public bathrooms.
到底在哪你才能尿尿?
Where can you pee?
我住的地方离这只有几里
I only live a few miles from here.
我以为人老了才会得关节炎
I thought arthritis was for old people.
幼年型类风湿性关节炎是自体免疫病
Jra's an autoimmune disease.
她的身体正在攻击自身
Her body's attacking itself,
引起了关节 眼部以及心脏的发炎
causing inflammation in the joints,,her eyes,and her heart.
可以治愈么?
Is it treatable?
可能对身体造成严重损害
It can be crippling.
但也可能完全康复
But it can also go into complete remission.
好在发现得早
Well, the good thing is we caught it early.
很可能会康复的
Gives her the best chance to have,a positive outcome.
爸--
Da--
别起来 小鹅
don't get up, goosey.
当心伤口缝线
Your stitches.
她中风了
She's having a stroke.
中风由大脑中动脉血栓引起
stroke was caused by a clot,in her middle cerebral artery.
给她用了组织型纤溶酶原激活物
Started her on tpa.
溶解血栓 希望能防止脑损伤
Should dissolve the clot and hopefully,prevent brain damage.
但在她恢复知觉之前 无法确知
But we won't know for sure,until she regains consciousness.
也可能会再一次中风
Or she has another stroke.
关节炎 心脏病
Arthritis...heart disease.
这小孩就不能表现得和年龄相称些?
- Why can't this  kid act her age?
幼年型类风湿性关节炎不影响血液
Jra doesn't affect the blood.
就是说血栓由其他病因引起
Means the clot's a symptom of something else.
是红血球增多症 她重度脱水
It's a symptom of polycythemia.,She's fully hydrated.
她的血液比煎饼面糊还要稠
Her blood's still thicker,than pancake batter.
血液粘稠解释中风
Thick blood explains the stroke.
可能引起自体免疫反应
Can also have caused an auto-immune response.
造成幼年型类风湿性关节炎
Which would explain the jra kicking into gear.
但这么会血液粘稠?
But what explains the thick blood?
缺氧使得身体生成过量红细胞
Lack of oxygen forces the body,to over produce red cells.
为什么会缺氧?
What explains the lack of oxygen?
一氧化碳气体 香烟烟雾
Carbon monoxide fumes,cigarette smoke.
- 不禁怀疑病人是烟民,- 爸爸可能是的
I doubt our patient's a smoker.,Dad could be.
他不是的
He's not.
- 嘴巴讲讲的,- 嘿!
- He says he's not.,- Hey!
别逼我用水管冲你们俩
Don't make me turn the hose on you two.
Chase说的没错
Chase is right.
你俩去家里查下,看看爸爸是不是隐秘的万宝路牛仔
You two go check the house.,See if dad's a closet marlboro man.
你是有心惩罚我们
You're intention ally punishing us.
让你做份内事来罚你,似乎有点不近人情
By making you do your job?,It does seem kind of cruel, doesn't it?
带个一氧化碳检测仪 查下有没漏气
Take along a carbon monoxide detector,to check for leaks.
至于你 给她用羟基脲控制红细胞生成
And you, start her on hydroxyurea,to control her red blood cell production.
翻一下中世纪版默克医疗手册,(最为广泛使用的医学参考书)
Dig out a merck manual,medieval edition,
会告你说放一到两品脱的血,就不会再有血栓
tell you how to drain a pint or two,so she doesn't clot again.
Cameron医生!
Dr. Cameron!
给你的花 谢谢你帮了我妹妹
I got you flowers.,For helping my sister.
你真好
That's so sweet.
- 你爸知道你在楼下么?,- 知道
- Does your dad know you're down here?,- Yes.
恭贺喜得麟儿
Congratulations on your bundle of joy.
你有什么忘记说了的?
Something you forgot to tell me?
你应该把花物归原处
You should take these back,to where you found them.
好吧
Okay.
麻烦你 务必让花和孩子都归原位
Excuse me, can you make sure these flowers,and this kid get back to where they belong?
- 好,- 谢谢
- Sure.,- Thanks.
走吧 快点
Let's go.Come on.
等下
Wait.
你就只是给她放血?
so you're just draining blood from her?
不检查 也不治疗?
You're not testing it,you're not fixing it?
你女儿的脉管系统血液充盈
Your daughter's vascular system,is engorged with blood.
放一些血降低中风发作的机率
Draining some reduces,the chances of another stroke.
同时给她用药
We're also starting her on a drug
抑制红细胞生成 就不用一直放血了
that suppresses the production of red cells,so we don't have to keep doing this.
她完全恢复的机会很大
Good chance she'll make a full recovery.
- 可她还没说过话,- 给她点时间
- She hasn't spoken yet.,- Give her time.
这是你儿子么?
this is your boy?
- 你去哪了?,- 探险
- Where have you been?,- Exploring.
- 回见,- 谢谢
- See ya.,- Thank you.
跟你说过的 不说一声不能乱跑
You know,you just can't run off,without telling me.
行 可以要两块钱么?
Okay.Can I have two dollars?
烤箱没戏 在得病前,早就能闻到气体异味
Oven's a long shot.They'd smell the gas,long before anyone got sick.
是 没错 我们跳过没戏的,House会很高兴
Yeah, right.House loves it when we skip,something 'cause it's a long shot.
为什么收下花 为什么亲他?
Why'd you take the flower?,Why'd you kiss him?
他做的事很可爱
He did something sweet.
- 花是偷来的,- 他只有八岁
- He stole flowers.,- He's eight.
你想让我心生嫉妒
You were trying to make me jealous.
是啊 我要你对我情浓意浓
Yeah, I want you to profs your love for me.
哦 且慢 你已经这么做了
Oh, wait,you already did that.
还弄得我要结束这段关系
And it caused me to end our relationship.
你这是纵容小贼
You're enabling a thief.
少年犯
And a delinquent.
学校通知
Letters from school.
打架 留堂 家长会
Fights, detentions,a parent conference.
哦 明白了
Oh, I know, I know.
男人不坏女人不爱
The bad boy is hard to resist.
只是单相思 没害处的
It's a crush.It's harmless.
- 没这么简单,- 你真让我获益良多
- It's never harmless.,- So I'm learning.
所以我们就这样了?
So this is us now?
相互攻击?
We snipe at each other?
我没有在找碴 我在找通风口
I'm not sniping,,I'm looking for a vent.
她的房间正好建在垃圾堆上
Her room's directly above the garage.
底下有很多一氧化碳气源
There's all sorts of co sources down there.
找到一个通风口
I found a vent.
里面好像有东西
I think there's something in it.
这不对劲
This isn't right.
你把我甩了 生气的不该是你
You dumped me.,You don't get to be mad.
我们在一起确实感觉不错
We had a really good thing.
是你坏了规则 惹我生气了
You broke the rules.I'm angry.
我会平复的
I'll get over it.
她被虐待
She's being abused.
带血的T恤不等于虐待
a bloody t-shirt doesn't equal abuse.
小孩常常会受伤的
Kids get hurt all the time.
这么多血?
That amount of blood?
哦 见鬼
Oh, crap.
你们两个又一条心了
You two are agreeing again.
父亲被繁重的工作压垮,妻子去年又过世了
Father's overwhelmed.Hectic job,,his wife passed away last year.
他很容易发泄在孩子头上
He could easily be taking it,out on the kids.
又或者是孩子流鼻血 抓了件T恤来擦
Or she had a nose bleed and,grabbed a t-shirt.
她觉得流鼻血太丢人
she's so ashamed of a nosebleed
硬是要把衣服藏在床下的通风口
she has to hide the evidence,in a vent under her bed.
她与外界隔离 哥哥一直是个麻烦鬼
She's socially isolated,,the brother's always in trouble.
典型的标志
It's classic signs.
但是没有体征,身体没有伤痕 没有任何瘀伤
But no physical signs.,No marks on her body.No bruises at all.
也许是性侵犯?
What if it's sexual?
应该打电话给社会福利署
We should call social services.
唉 糟透了
Well, this sucks.
这或是虐待 或者不是
Either it's abuse or it's not abuse.
或者是一种症状 或者完全无关
Which means either it's a symptom,or it's completely irrelevant.
无论哪种情况 都得费个半天搞清楚
Either way,we gotta waste half a day,figuring out which.
全面身体检查
Full physical exam.
查一下可能遗漏的瘀伤
Look for bruises we may have missed.
检查口腔 做阴道检查
Check her mouth and do a vaginal exam.
没有父亲同意,不能对六岁孩子做阴道检查
We can't do a vaginal exam on a,six-year-old without the dad's consent.
如果是他施虐 绝无可能同意
And if he's abusing her,,he'll never say yes.
世事无绝对
Never is just "reven" spelled backwards.
你虐待过你女儿吗?
Have you been abusing your daughter?
什么 你怎么会...
What?Why would you...
这是在她床下的通风口找到的
we found this hidden in a vent under her bed.
我对此一无所知
I don't know anything about this.
也许是流鼻血
Maybe she had a bloody nose.
我们需要检查她是否受过虐待
We need to examine her for abuse.
不是真的以为我...
You can't really think I...
也许是你 或是学校的流氓,变态的邻居
maybe you,maybe the school bully,,maybe the creepy neighbor.
总之你没有尽责
I'm guessing you're not paying as,much attention as you should be.
你都不知道你儿子现在在哪?
You even know where your son is right now?
他在这里 一分钟前还在的
Yeah, he was here just...here a minute ago.
她没有被虐待
She isn't being abused.
很遗憾 这回答不能让人信服
Unfortunately, that answer doesn't help me.
如果你虐待过她 自然会撒谎的
If you have abused her,,you're obviously gonna lie about it.
我没有说谎!
I'm not lying!
- 我们需要做阴道检查,- 不行
- We need to do a vaginal exam.,- No,
她快要死了 还不能说话,而你们还在这种事情上浪费时间?
she may be dying,she still can't talk,,and you're gonna waste your time with this?
你同意了 我们就花几小时做检查
You consent,and we waste a,few hours doing the exam,
如果你拒绝 我就叫社会福利署的人来
or you refuse and I call social services.
他们会花三天调查
And they waste three days,doing the investigation
最后他们还是要做这个检查
which ends with them doing the exam anyway.
张大嘴巴 我要看里面
I'm gonna look inside your mouth.,Open wide.
接下来要检查胸和背 可以么?
I need to look at your chest,and your back next, okay?
我知道你不能讲话,如果害怕了就示意我停下
I know you can't talk so,stop me if you get scared.
入院前 有人伤害过你么?
Before you came here,,did anyone hurt you?
让你流血?
Make you bleed?
现在我要检查你的阴道,能谅解么?
I need to look in your vagina now.,Do you understand?
我是医生 所以没有关系的 好么?
I'm a doctor,so it's okay, all right?
屈膝 脚踝并拢
Bend your knees,keep your ankles together.
膝盖侧向一边 可以么?
And just let your knees fall,to the side, okay?
哦 天哪
Oh, my god.
生殖器区尽是割伤
She has cuts all over her,genital area.Like slices.
一些差不多愈合了 一些是新的
Some are almost healed,but some are new.
可能是她自己弄得
She could be doing it to herself.
她太小 不会割伤自己的
She's a little young to be cutting.
她太小 不会中风
She's a little young for a stroke.
抑郁解释了割伤
Depression accounts for the cuts.
性侵犯解释了抑郁
Molestation accounts for the depression.
割伤能解释这么多血吗?
But do the cuts account for all that blood?
伤口不够深
They weren't deep enough.
就是说她被割伤了 却并非出血的原因?
So she's getting cut,,but that's not the source of the blood?
很可能是强行侵入
The other obvious source is,forcible penetration.
讲得通出血 讲不通割伤
Obvious source of the blood,not the cuts.
没有撕裂 根本没有任何证据
And there was no tearing.,There was no evidence at all.
无法解释的割伤和出血
So we have no explanation,for the cuts or the blood.
他到哪去了?
Where is he?
如果假设从一开始就错了呢?
What if our original assumption was wrong?
怎么说?
Meaning what?
在通风口找到一件沾满血的T恤
We found a t-shirt covered with blood,hidden in the heating vent.
怎么知道是她的?
How do we know it's even hers?
她爸爸确认了
Her dad identified it.
我指的不是T恤 而是血
Not the shirt, the blood.
- 这...是尿检结果吗?,- 是的
- Are--are those the urine test results?,- Yes.
- 那么...,- 我要给你验血
- And...,- I'm going to ask you for some blood.
为什么?
Why?
看你是否会回答,公共场合我的血流不出来
To see if your answer will be,,I can't bleed in public.
这不是你的尿 对吧?
This wasn't your urine,was it?
我为什么给你别人的尿样?
Why would I give you someone else's urine?
通常是因为你在用类固醇
The usual reason is because,you're on steroids.
我不是运动员
I'm not an athlete.
第二个大行其道的原因是你吸毒
Second favorite reason,is because you're on drugs.
- 我没吸,- 我吸
- I'm not.,- I am.
第三个大行其道的原因是你有保险
Third favorite reason is,,you have insurance,
但你相好的没有
but your friend eggs benedict doesn't.
所以你向医生复述,你相好的描述的症状
So eggs describes a list of symptoms,and you repeat them to a doctor.
真是愚蠢至极 因为这里是义诊
Which is particularly stupid,because this is a free clinic.
我需要你 现在
Need you.Now.
这儿没我的事了
My work here is done.
我没事吧 是糖尿病吗?
Am I okay?Is it diabetes?
不是 你怀孕了
No, you're pregnant.
六岁的虐待受害者,你居然不通知社会福利署?
Six-year-old abuse victim,and you haven't called social services?
她可能被虐 太可怕了
She might have been abused?,That's horrifying.
你眼睛下面干嘛涂这么多遮瑕粉?
Why are you wearing extra concealer,under your eyes?
法律明文规定 一旦怀疑病人遭到虐待,就得通知当局
The law is clear.You suspect abuse,,you call the authorities.
施虐者可能就坐在她身旁,而你却不行动?
You don't proceed as usual while the,possible abuser sits by her bedside.
爸爸同意检查 表明不是他干的
Dad consented to the exam,,which means it's not the dad.
你昨晚在外面待到多晚?
How late were you out last night?
干这种事的总是爸爸,另外我不用宵禁
It's always the dad.,And I don't have a curfew.
你的小妹妹一夜偷欢?
Panty hamster get a spin on its wheel?
我去看戏了
I went to a play.
House 你给我回办公室
House, you are going back to your office.
打电话通知社会福利署
You are picking up your phone,,calling social services,
举报可疑的虐待事件
and you are reporting suspected abuse.
明白了吗?
Do you understand?
哪出戏?
What play?
你想跟Cuddy做爱
You're trying to have sex with cuddy.
- 要炸薯条吗?,- 你带她去看戏
- Fries?,- You took her to a play.
带女人去看戏只是为了...
You only take women to plays because--
不 你才只为这原因带女人看戏
no, you only take women to plays,for that reason.
那是你的理论
That's your theory.
好吧 那你干嘛带她去看戏?
Okay,then why did you take her to a play?
- 她是我朋友,- 有阴道的朋友
- She's a friend.,- A friend with a squish mitten.
可以跟异性做朋友
It is possible to have a friend,of the opposite sex.
歪理邪说!
Blasphemer!
她不是异性朋友 而是异类
She's not a friend of the opposite sex,,she's a different species.
她是管理人
She's an administrator.
一旦完事就吃掉你的脑袋
She's gonna eat your head,after she's done.
是的 我跟她睡过
Yes, I slept with her.
- 当真?,- 没有
- Seriously?,- No.
是的 你睡过她
Yes, you did.
是 没错
Yes, I did.
当真?
Seriously?
没有 你有毛病 House
No.You got a problem, house.
刚测完LucyT恤上的血
We just tested the blood on lucy's t-shirt.
内含大量子宫内膜细胞
It's full of endometrial cells.
这么说不是她的血
So it's not her blood.
也测了 血是她的
We tested that too.It is.
你六岁的病人?
Your six-year-old patient?
是经血
It's menstrual blood.
她进入了青春期
She's started puberty.
怎么会没上小学 就进入青春期呢?
how can someone start puberty,before they even start the first grade?
两年前她还裹着尿布
She was in diapers two years ago.
出于某种原因 她体内分泌大量荷尔蒙
For some reason, her body,has too much sex hormone.
造成生殖系统紊乱
Caused her reproductive system,to get confused.
过早开始发育
Start operating prematurely.
得找出荷尔蒙的诱因 加以清除
We need to find out the source,of the hormones and cut it off.
她还那么年幼
She's so young.
我甚至都没...跟她谈过性
I haven't even...talked to her about sex.
我怀疑她知不知道什么是生理期
I doubt she even knows what a period is.
这种事女孩讲给妈妈听
Girls talk to their moms about that.
你会没事的 小鹅
You're going to be okay, goosey.
我爱你
I love you.
我...
I...
要...
want...
果汁
juice.
她来了月经 但不知道是什么
She got her period,and didn't know what it was.
她又害怕又困惑
She was scared and confused.
朋友让她把T恤塞进内裤
Her friend told her to put a t-shirt,in her underwear.
开始长阴毛时
When she started growing pubic hair,
她偷了爸爸的剃须刀想把毛剃掉
she snuck daddy's razor and tried,to shave it off.
她显然忘了偷剃须膏
Apparently, forgot to sneak the,shaving cream.
很可能是瘤
Tumors, most likely.
垂体腺瘤可以让她的激素水平升得很高
A pituitary adenoma would send,her hormone level sky-high.
70年代在波多黎各
in puerto rico in the '70s,
家禽内含雌激素 使孩子纷纷乳房发育
there was an epidemic of kids growing,breasts because of estrogen in the poultry.
如果诱因在食物里 症状会流行
If it was in the food,,it would be an epidemic.
- 只有一个孩子,- 她才六岁 个子很小
- We've got one kid.,- She's six.She's tiny.
她吃鸡柳条和牛奶过日子
She lives on chicken fingers and milk.
爸爸似乎不爱看食品说明
Dad doesn't look like the type to,read labels.
或许他买回的食物里全是激素
He's probably buying stuff,packed full of hormones.
完美的论点
Excellent argument.
这是个瘤
It's a tumor.
有各种环境诱因 杀虫剂 豆制品
There's all sorts of environmental sources:,Pesticides, soy products.
有些洗发精就象装在瓶里的胎盘
Some shampoos are basically a,placenta in a bottle.
瘤不在她脑袋里 就在生殖系统里,做核磁共振
If the tumor's not in her brain,,it's her reproductive tract.Get an mri.
- 我能否至少...,- 浪费时间?
- Can I at least--,- waste your time?
如果你不浪费时间 就不是你了
Wouldn't recognize you if you didn't.
额叶皮层没问题 移到尾部
frontal cortex is clean.Moving caudally.
明说吧 是Cameron跟我分手的
For the record,,cameron's the one who broke it off.
没兴趣听
Not interested.
视丘下部没有肿块
No masses in the hypothalamus.
我想要的更多
I wanted more.
她和我意见相左
She didn't share my feelings.
我现在和她一样
I feel like I'm in a similar position.
垂体没问题
Pituitary's clean.
你是个白痴
You're an idiot.
她要么是撒谎 要么是真的没动感情
Either she's lying,,or she's actually emotionally detached.
你看哪个更像Cameron?
Which one sounds more like cameron to you?
都不像
Neither.
你得选一个
You have to choose one.
左卵巢有亮点
There's a bright spot on the left ovary.
看起来像实性瘤
Looks like a solid tumor.
我的信登出来了
They printed my letter.
你说得对
You were right.
我当然对 说什么来着?
Of course I was.,What are we talking about?
- 我的信登出来了,- 棒极了
- They printed my letter.,- Great.
你想看她一丝不挂
You wanna see her naked.
不不 她想看我一丝不挂
No, no, no.She wants to see me naked.
她送我鲜花
She sent me flowers.
她不过是感谢你带她看戏
She's just thanking you for the play.
有些人会产生感激之情
See, some people feel,an emotion called gratitude--
- 里面有张卡片,- 我怀疑
- there's a card.,- I suspected.
卡片告诉你花是谁送的
Explains how you knew who they were from.
"让我们再干一次吧...尽快 XX Lisa"
"Let's do it again...soon.Xx, lisa."
X代表亲吻 对吗?
X's are the kisses, right?
不 我认为代表拥抱 O代表亲吻
No, I think they're the gs.,The o's are the kisses.
不 X肯定是亲吻
No, no.The x's are definitely the kisses.
"尽快"则独立成句
"Soon" is its own sentence.
我得走了!
I gotta go!
我会想念你的
I'll miss you.
你是个好朋友
You were a good friend.
我的信登出来了
They printed my letter.
- 戏怎么样 林肯夫人,- Wilson怎么了? (林肯在剧院被刺)
- How was the play,mrs. Lincoln?,- What's up with wilson?
- 有点受惊而已,- 为什么?
- He's just a little freaked.,- Why?
我送花给他
I sent him flowers.
Jasper 你不该来这儿
Jasper, you' not supposed to be up here.
那个医生是你男朋友?
Is that other doctor your boyfriend?
不是
No.
你爸爸也许在找你
Your dad's probably looking for you.
现在他操心的事够多的了
He's got enough to worry about right now.
你喜欢他吗?
Do you like him?
他是我朋友
He's a friend.
是那种喜欢吗?
Do you like him like him?
我该把你带回你爸爸身边
We should get you back to your dad.
我把这个放下就带你去
Let me put this down,and I'll take you there.
我可以做你男朋友
I could be your boyfriend.
我...
I...
这对跟你一般年纪的小姑娘不公平
think that wouldn't be fair,to the girls your own age.
他看着像是个傻子
He seems like a tool.
他不是 别说粗话
He's not.And that's rude.
我带你找爸爸去
I'm taking you back to your father.
体积不大 只有1厘米宽
Mass is small--about a centimeter across.
插入活检针
firing the biopsy needle.
- 你刺到动脉了,- 没有
- You nick an artery?,- No.
室颤 没有脉搏了
She's in v-tach;no pulse.
充电50焦耳 闪!
Charging 50.Clear!
闪!
Clear!
心律不齐肯定是身体对羟基脲的反应
Arrhythmia must've been a reaction,to the hydroxyurea.
必须停止药物
We have to stop the drug therapy.
她的骨髓会再次制造过多的血细胞
Her bone marrow will just go back,to over producing blood cells.
她会再次中风 就得持续给她放血
She'll keep having strokes,and,we'll have to keep bleeding her...forever.
切除肿瘤 激素水平恢复正常,症状就会消失
We resect the tumor,hormone levels,go back to normal,her symptoms go away
好计划
Great plan...
可惜她的肿块不是瘤
except for the fact,that her tumor's not a tumor.
是良性囊肿
It's a benign cyst.
如果不是肿瘤 就只剩下环境因素了
If it's not a tumor,,that just leaves an environmental source.
又要熬夜了
Feeling another late night.
我走了 你们俩干吧
I'm gonna leave you two alone.
- 你开什么玩笑?,- 怎么了
-You're kidding me,right?,-What?
答案就在眼前 只不过要找寻下
The answer's right there.,It's just a question of finding it.
多我一个也没用
You don't need me for that.
不要摩卡奇诺咖啡
Don't get the mochaccino.
很难喝,自动售货机里放的是热巧克力
They screwed up,and put hot chocolate in the dispenser.
- 谢谢,- 不客气
-Thank you.,-You were right.
8岁的小孩捏了我屁股
The eight-year-old kid grabbed my ass.
我不该鼓励他的
I shouldn't have encouraged him.
我也曾是小男孩 知道他们怎么想
Well,I was a boy once.,I know how they think.
- 你8岁时就性变态?,- 11岁时吧
-You were a pervert at eight?,-Maybe 11.
我没想过 你会受伤
I didn't realize you were gonna get hurt.
我不该误导你
I'm sorry I misled you.
你没有
You didn't.
你对我有感觉
You have feelings for me.
你一次次回来找我
You come back to me again and again.
为了性 简单的 肉体的
For sex.,It's a simple,physical--
你对小动物和,几乎不认识的病人都有感情
you have feelings for puppies,and patients that you barely know.
何况是一个共事了3年
But when it comes to a guy,that you've worked with for three years,
做爱 一同过夜的男人
had sex with,,spent the night with...
你能说没感觉吗?
you're telling me you feel nothing?
一点没有?
Absolutely nothing?
放开她 不许碰她!
Get away from her!,Don't touch her!
- 你再碰她 我就杀了你!,- Jasper!
-I'll kill you if you touch her!,-Jasper!
拉开他 他咬我
Get him off!  Ah!,He's biting me! Get him off!
他会怎么做?!
what is he gonna do?!
他停下 站在围绳上望着对手
he stopped,and looked at him from the top rope.
他在测角度!
But now he's scaling!
不可能!
no way!
有人要死了?
Somebody better be dying.
Lucy的哥哥爱上我了 他咬伤了Chase
Lucy's big brother's got a crush on me,so he bit the crap out of chase.
我会在乎 是因为?
and I care because...?
也许你想知道
Just thought you might wanna know
你的下属被反社会份子攻击了
when one of your employees,gets attacked by a sociopath.
被蜜蜂 猴子攻击还有点兴趣,被反社会份子攻击 没
bees or monkeys,yes.,Sociopaths,no.
已经分不清他是不是被击倒了
doesn't have sense,enough to know he wasn't pinned.
他不是人 是怪兽
he's not a man. He is a monster!
不可能!
no way!
一定要重看一遍
we gotta take another look at this...
- 你好,- 他不是反社会
-Hello.,-He's not a sociopath.
你怎么知道?
How do you know?
他的行为合乎逻辑
he's acting logically.
他爱上你
He's got a crush on you.
争勇好斗
He's being aggressive about it.
不是通常的好斗
Not just regular aggressive...
还是被激素冲昏头的好斗
he's out-of-his-mind-on-hormones aggressive.
- 你认为他,- 最好找出女孩的病因
-You think he's--,-you better figure out what's killing the girl...
因为她哥也得了
because her brother's got it too.
Jasper的睾丸激素水平,是正常8岁男孩的100倍
jasper's got 100 times more testosterone,than a healthy,eight-year-old.
但检查了脑部和生殖道,没有分泌腺肿瘤
But we scanned his brain and reproductive tract--,no hormone-secreting tumors.
不奇怪 什么可能性更大
Not surprised.What's more likely?
兄妹在一时间得了相同的肿瘤
Brother and sister get the same type of tumor,at exactly the same time
他们玩同一个有毒的沙盒吗?
or they both play in the same toxic sandbox?
你这么想也可以,只要你完全忽略
yes,you would think that if,for some reason,,you were completely unaware of
我们花整晚检测他家的所有东西
the fact we spent the entire night testing,everything from that home.
都呈阴性
It was all negative.
你回家了?
You went home?
有一套 委派别人
Good for you.Delegate.
我们不是他的下属
We're not his subordinates.
显得更有一套了
Making it all the more impressive.
会不会是遗传?
What if it's genetic?
不太会是巧合 两个孩子有
Anyone else think it's more than,a coincidence these kids have symptoms
脑瘤的症状 母亲也死于此病因
that could be caused by a brain tumor,,which is exactly what killed their mom?
都说了没有肿瘤 扫描了两人的大脑
you just said there were no tumors.,We scanned both their brains.
没有异状
They looked clean.
他们妈妈也是 直到病情恶化了
So did their moms,until it didn'T.
不可能是遗传
It can't be genetic.
- 妈妈没有相同的症状,- 她有
-Mom had none of the same symptoms.,-Yes,she did.
如果症状是长阴毛
If the symptoms were pubic hair
- 来月经,- 太荒唐了
-and menstruation...,-That's ridiculous.
如果来月经是癌症症状
If menstruation is a symptom of brain cancer,
我也该做化疗了
than I should be on chemo right now.
这才荒唐 你骨瘦如柴 不会来月经
That's ridiculous.,You're way too skinny to be menstruating.
也许妈妈有别的病症
what if the mom had other problems...
她的医生基于她快死了 就忽视了
symptoms her doctors ignored on account of,the fact she was already dying?
翻出她的医学档案,找出和我们病人的相似点
Pull all her medical records.,Find any similarities to our patients.
当鼻揍小屁孩 让他出点血,就不会像他妹妹那样中风了
Punch the little braton the nose,so he doesn't have a stroke like his sister
- 我没病,- 我试着保证你没病
-I'm not sick.,-Just trying to keep you that way.
我要Cameron医生检查
I want dr. Cameron to do mine.
相信我 你可不想她现在来宰了你
Trust me.,You don't want her cutting you right now.
Jasper的行为异常
So...jasper's behavioral issues...
是睾丸激素升高引起
could be a function of the increased,testosterone.
希望查出原因 他就能心情好些
Hopefully,he'll be a delight,as soon as we figure this out.
肚子疼!
My tummy hurts!,It hurts!
不会的 别闹脾气
No,it doesn'T.,Don't be such a baby.
- 肚子疼,- 肚子哪一块?
-My tummy hurts!,-Where in your tummy?
疼死了
It hurts!It hurts!
胰腺的囊肿导致腹痛
Stomach pain is from a cyst in her pancreas.
在肾脏发现2个 在肺发现一个
I found two more in her kidneys,and one in her lung.
48小时前都没有
They weren't there 48 hours ago.
激素让她身体短路了
The hormones are making her body go haywire.
要是在脑子和心脏有囊肿 就死定了
She gets one in her brain or heart,,she's dead.
别有压力
No pressure though.
妈妈在得癌症前很健康
Mom was perfectly healthy,until she got cancer.
孩子的病症 她一个都没有
She had none of the symptoms the kids have.
不是遗传 也不是环境
It's not genetic.,It's not environmental.
肯定是脑垂体瘤
It's gotta be a pituitary adenoma.
这是完全能说通
Yes,that would make complete sense,if we had one.
没扫描到不代表没有
Just because we haven't found anything,on the scan doesn't mean it's not there
该切除她的脑垂腺
You should remove her pituitary gland.
兄妹两个 同样的症状
Two siblings,same condition.
一定是遗传或环境
It's gotta be genetic or environmental.
两个方向同时切入,现在只剩下环境了
We add in the same time,and we're back to just environmental.
可是环境什么也没查出 说得通吗?
yes,and that would make complete sense,if there was anything in her environment.
只因还没有找到
That's 'cause we haven't found anything yet.
她脱离环境4天了 还在恶化
she's been out of her environment for four,days and she's still getting worse.
- 我要取得父亲的同意,- 不行!
-I'm getting the father's consent.,-No!
没有证据
We have no evidence.
按你House步骤来的
This is your process,house.
你问2加2得多少
You asked us what two plus two is.
排除了所有数字除了4
We've eliminated every number except for four.
她得做脑科手术
She needs brain surgery.
脑垂体给卵巢信号 制造性激素
The ovaries produce sex hormones in response,to a signal from the pituitary gland
既然卵巢没问题 最有可能--
Since we know the ovaries are fine,,the most likely cause--
"最有可能"意味着她要,在你小女儿的脑子里翻查
"most likely" means she wants to root around,inside your little girl's brain
能不能奏效可没有保证
without any guarantee that it'll work.
所以她推迟对你儿子下手
That's why she's holding off on doing your son.
House医生明白 没有别的办法了
Dr. House knows that unfortunately,,we've ruled out every other option.
- 需要切除lucy的垂体,- 还有谁探访过孩子?
-We need to resect lucy's pituitary before--,-who else visits these kids?
- 他们在本地没有亲戚,- 有女朋友吗?
-They don't have any family in town.,-You got a girlfriend?
没人来探访过
No one visits.
- 学校?,- 他俩上不同的学校 House 我--
-School?,-They don't go to the same school.House,I've--
- 保姆?,- 没有
-nanny?,-They don't have one.
他们放学后去托儿所,但其他孩子没得病
They go to an after-school day care,,but none of the other kids are sick.
尚未
Yet.
你儿子发病比女儿慢了一倍
It took your son twice as long,to develop symptoms as your daughter.
也许别的孩子发病慢
Maybe the other kids are just slow.
- 再等的话 你女儿会死的,- 如果按她的做
-We wait and your daughter may die.,-She does this,
你女儿余生都要进行激素替代治疗
your daughter will need hormone-replacement,therapy for the rest of her life
治疗很有效
The treatments are extremely effective.
她的生活会基本正常
She should lead a relatively normal life.
这不是每个家长的梦想吗?
And isn't that every parent's dream?
让孩子能长成基本正常
To have a kid grow up to be relatively normal?
我丈夫死于甲状腺癌 后来转移到脑部
My husband died of thyroid cancer,that metastasized to his brain.
我目睹了
I've been there.
知道有多可怕
I know how terrifying this can be.
这是救你女儿命的最佳方法了
I am telling you that this is your best,chance to save your daughter's life.
你耍了招死老公的伎俩
You did not just play the dead husband card.
我的妻子死了
My wife died
因为她签署了同意书,我不想她签的
because she signed a consent form,that I didn't want her to sign.
死翘翘了
Died.
谢谢
Thank you.
你怎么知道?
How did you know?
知道什么?
Know what?
其他孩子没事?
That the other kids weren't sick.
- 这四天你都在这儿,- 只是
-You've been here for four days.,-I just--
我没听人说起
I would've heard.
明白了
Right.
- 你私处长毛了吗?,- Janie小姐!
-Do you have hair on your special place?,-Miss janie!
有何贵干?
Can I help you?
我是医生
I'm a doctor.
你这里一个孩子病了,我来找原因
One of your kids are sick,and I need to know why.
你认为是在这儿染上的?
You think they got sick here?
我认为你和他们爸爸约会
I think you're dating their dad.
他告诉你了?
He told you?
没有
No...
我不在乎他为什么隐瞒
and I don't really care why he didn'T.
我想知道你隔多久去他们家,带去了些什么
I just need to know how often you go to,their house and what you bring.
- 我没有,- 洗发水 香皂
-I don't.,-Shampoos,fancy soaps?
- 孩子翻你的包,- 我从没去过他们家
-Kids get in your bag?,-I've never been to their house.
他们妈妈刚死
They just lost their mom.
有点太快了
And we thought it was too soon.
你为什么盯着我?
Why are you staring at me?
唇蜡除毛?
Lip wax?
我在午饭时去弄的
I just had it done over lunch.
美甲?
Mani-pedi?
只是脱毛
No...just the wax.
女人去脱毛 放纵自己,这是美丽仪式的一部分
Women get a wax,it's part of the,whole self-indulgent,beauty ritual.
连同美甲 蒸脸 黄瓜面膜
Pedicure,steam,cucumber masks.
哪有人趁午饭时间溜出去唇蜡除毛
No one runs out of lunch just,to get a lip wax,
除非你醒来发现自己像yosemite sam,(卡通人物 长胡子矮子劫匪)
unless you woke up looking like,yosemite sam.
你真狠
You're an ass.
- Cameron,- 总是老爸惹的祸
-Cameron.,-It's always the dad.
女人脸上多毛
Excess facial hair in women.
是激素失调的明显信号
It's a clear sign of hormonal imbalance.
和孩子的情况一致
Exactly what the little kiddies have.
托儿所有什么不对劲?
Is there something wrong at the,day care center?
是你的裤裆里有点不对劲
There's something wrong in your pants.
她比我年轻很多
She's a lot younger than I am.
我用了
I...use A...
壮阳乳霜 来配合她,这有关系吗?
male-enhancement cream to keep up with her.,What does this have to do--
你就没想过用开处方药,而不是用睾丸激素充气泵?
it never occurred to you to get a prescription,instead of some  pumper loaded with testosterone?
我把它放在健身房
I keep it at the gym.
每天淋浴时用 完全依照瓶子上写的
I apply it daily in the shower,just like it says on the bottle.
从没放在家里 没有接近过孩子
It's never been in my home.,It's obviously never been near the kids.
- 但你接近,- 已经说过了
-But you have.,-We been through that.
我不是性变态 也不是恋童癖
I'm not a pervert or a pedophile!
身体30%的废物从皮肤排出
30% of our waste is excreted through our skin.
听上去很高
That sounds high.
所以你吃了大蒜会发臭
That's why you stink after eating garlic.
杰克连续一周给豆茎浇水,(童话 杰克栽魔豆 豆茎长上天)
Jack waters his bean stalk every day for a week.
他的毛孔在一个月里分泌豆腐
He's oozing bean curd out of his pores for a month.
每次你抱小家伙
Every time you gave the little tykes a hug,
都给他们一剂睾丸激素
you gave them a dose of testosterone.
对你是少量
Small for you,
但幼小的身体承受不了
but more than their little bodies can handle.
是我造成的?
So...I did this to them?
- 握住他们的手就会?,- 是
-Just...holding their hands?,-Uh-huh.
如果停用呢?
If I stop using it?
你会软趴趴 他们会没事
You'll be floppy,,they'll be fine.
他会是8岁的样子
-Give it back,-he'll still be eight.
- 没事吧?,- 没什么
-You okay?,-Yeah,I think so.
- 对Cuddy说了?,- 还没有 不知道怎么说
-Talk to cuddy?,-No,not yet.I don't know what to say
坦白就好
Just be straight with her.
我还不确信
I'm not sure what that is.
控制不住地想她
I can't stop thinking about her.
想什么?
In what way?
也许她是对的
Maybe she's right.Maybe...
也许值得冒险探究
Maybe this is worth exploring.
- 你确定她对你有感觉,- 她送花给我
-Are you sure that she feels--,-she sent me flowers.
该怎么办 说什么好?
How do i do this?,What do I say?
Cameron会劝你说出你的感受
Cameron would tell you to say how you feel.
我么就劝你灌醉她
Me,I'd get her drunk.
我什么也不说
I'm not gonna say anything.
走进她办公室
I'm just gonna walk...into her office
就吻她
and I'm gonna kiss her.
很大胆
That's A...bold move.
Cuddy喜欢大胆
Cuddy likes bold.
对 耍嘴皮子 你会说傻气的话
Yeah,you're right.If you spoke,,you'd say something stupid.
我要么有个女朋友 要么就被解雇
Yeah,I mean,,I'll either get a girlfriend or get fired.
成
Okay.
就这么着
Yeah,okay.Okay.
行
All right.
你 你!
You!,You...you!
你让我这么做?
You were gonna let me do that?!
你的论据有理有据
You made a compelling argument.
- 是你送花给我!,- 因为你请她去看戏了
-You sent those flowers to me!,-Yes,because you took her to a play.
因为你真的想走过去吻她
Because actually you do want,to march down there and kiss her.
- 不 我不想,- 有 你想的
-No,I don't!,-Yes,you do!
你说得对
You're right.
- 真的?,- 不
-Seriously?,-No.
你是混蛋
You're a jerk.
- 晚安 Wilson,- 晚安 House
-Night,wilson.,-Night,house.
很漂亮
They're beautiful.
我想了想你说的
I thought about what you said.
我不想和你交往
And I really don't want a relationship with you.
我知道
I know.
我也知道你喜欢花
I also know you like flowers.
不理解花季少女和老人家的爱情
I don't get the whole may-december thing.
得了吧 这最多是花季少女和大叔
Give him a break.,It's may-october at worst.
为什么不能是大妈对大叔?
Well,why can't it be october-october?
花季五月是热力散发的时候
May is when things start to get hot.
如果这男人不是拼命想配合,小他一半的女人
If that guy wasn't trying so hard,to keep up with a woman half his age,
就不会差点害死小孩
he wouldn't have almost killed both his kids.
男人搞点什么玩艺,一些孩子会死去 生命循环
Guy gets a little something-something...,couple of kids have to die...circle of life.
那么多人
So many people.
那么多精力激情 为了寻找某个人
So much energy and drama,just trying to find someone
找到的永远不是对的人
who's almost never the right person anyway
不该这么难
It just...shouldn't be so hard.
我有戏票
I got tickets to a play.